{
    "subject": "resource/Mishti",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/India",
    "human_readable": "Mishti was born in India.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8446617126464844,
            "question": "Is Mishti Indian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8440389633178711,
            "question": "Where was Mishti born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6039313673973083,
            "question": "Do you know if Mishti has any family members still living in India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5397465825080872,
            "question": "What country is Mishti from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41761723160743713,
            "question": "What are some popular traditions in India that Mishti might be familiar with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4132393002510071,
            "question": "Where might Mishti have grown up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.392915815114975,
            "question": "Would Mishti's birthplace influence her perspectives on the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20992504060268402,
            "question": "Do you know anything about Mishti's upbringing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1727595031261444,
            "question": "What kind of cultural influences might Mishti have experienced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1630295366048813,
            "question": "Could Mishti speak other languages besides English?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mishti was born in India.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8147_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of cultural influences might Mishti have experienced?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8147_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know anything about Mishti's upbringing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8147_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would Mishti's birthplace influence her perspectives on the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8147_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8147_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8147_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8147_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8147_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8147_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8147_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8147_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8147_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8147_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8147_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of whether the triple \"Mishti was born in India\" is supported by the documents:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents mention Mishti's birthplace as being located in either West Bengal (in some cases referred to as Calcutta) or Kolkata, which are both cities in India. Therefore, it can be inferred that Mishti was indeed born in India."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents provide information that supports the statement \"Mishti was born in India.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention her birthplace as Calcutta (now Kolkata), which is a city in West Bengal, India."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}